Guide to the New-York Historical Society Geographic Images Collection circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: New York City Views - Manhattan
  - Subseries ID: MANHATTAN - OVERSIZE MATERIAL
    - Manhattan - Oversize Prints - General Views
      - Kipp and Brown's Stage as it Appeared in Passing the Astor House on the 16th of June 1845, Henry R. Robinson, lithographer, published by William H. Hoyt (Folder OS FF 509)
      - New York. Taken from the North West Angle of Fort Columbus, Governor's Island, engraved by Papprill after Catherwood, 1846 (Folder OS FF510)
        Four copies, one in color
      - New York from Staten Island, C.W. Burton, lithographer, published by Sarony & Major, 1849 (Folder OS FF 511)
      - Cliff Street, New York, lithographed and published by G. & W. Endicott, circa 1850 (Folder OS FF 509)
      - Bay of New York Taken from the Battery, E. Valois, lithographer, after John Bornet, 1851 (Folder OS FF 511)
      - New York Crystal Palace for the Exhibition of the Industry of All Nations, drawn by A. Fay, printed by A. Fay and M. Ballin, published by Emil Seitz, 1853 (Folder OS FF 512)
      - New York Crystal Palace, 1853 (Folder OS FF 512)
        according to a printed note, this print was created from a contemporary view, block printed in colors on wall paper. It was used as a fireboard to be placed in front of a fireplace in the summer season.
      - Interior View of the New York Crystal Palace for the Exhibition of the Industry of All Nations, Executed by Thomas Benecke and A. Weingartner, lithography by Nagel and Weingartner, published by Goupil and Co., 1853 (Folder OS FF 512)
      - Panorama of the Harbor of New York, Staten Island and the Narrows, John Bornet, lithographer, published by Goupil, 1854 (Folder OS FF 511)
      - New York, engraved by Himely, after John William Hill, 1855 (Folder *OS FF 523)
        Three copies; Super Oversize, special handling required
      - New York, engraved by Cottram, after John William Hill, 1855 (Folder *OS FF 523)
        Two copies; Super oversize, requires special handling
      - New-York, Winter Scene in Broadway, engraved by P. Girardet after H. Sebron, 1857 (Folder OS FF 513)
        Four copies, one in color.
      - Martel's New York Central Park, printed by Eno Lithographing Co., published by William H. Shields, 1864 (Folder OS FF 514)
      - Bartlett & Greene's Free and Bonded Warehouses and Elevators, Endicott & Co. Lithographers, circa 1880 (Folder OS FF 514)
        shows the E.B. Bartlett & Co. warehouse in Red Hook, Brooklyn. Two copies.
      - Broadway, North from Cortlandt Street and Maiden Lane, American Photo-Lithograph Co., circa 1885 (Folder OS FF 514)
      - Grand Birds Eye View of the Great East River Suspension Bridge, Currier & Ives, 1885 (Folder OS FF 515)
        Two copies, one in color.
      - "Liberty Enlightening the World" Bartholdi's Colossal Statue on Bedlow's Island, New York Harbor, drawn by Harry Fenn, published by Harper and Brothers, 1886 (Folder OS FF 515)
        supplement to Harper's Weekly, October 30, 1886.
      - The Great East River Suspension Bridge, Currier & Ives, 1886 (Folder OS FF 515)
      - The Polo Grounds, New York, Season of 1887, Thomas Fleming, delineator, published by New York Litho. Co. (Folder OS FF 515)
      - Centennial Military Parade - West Point Cadets passing the reviewing stand in Madison Square, drawn by T. De Thulstrup, Harper's Weekly, 1889 (Folder OS FF 516)
      - Centennial Naval Parade in the Upper Bay - the U.S.S. Despatch and her convoy passing Governor's Island, as seen from the Washington Building, drawn by Charles Graham, Harper's Weekly, 1889 (Folder OS FF 516)
      - The Grant Monument, Riverside Park on the Hudson, New York City, drawn by Maurice Ingres, published by V. Haurie-Emes, 1891 (Folder OS FF 517)
        Two copies, one marked "artist's proof."
      - New York Columbian Celebration Naval Review, drawn by Victor Perard, from Harper's Weekly, 1892 (Folder OS FF 516)
      - The Day Before the Great Naval Review - the Fleet passing Castle William on it's way up the Hudson, drawn by Victor Perard, Harper's Weekly, 1893 (Folder OS FF 516)
      - A Base Ball Game [at the Polo Grounds], after Henry Sandham, published by Boussod Valadon & Co., 1897 (Folder OS FF 517)
      - View of the Naval Parade Passing Grant's Tomb in Celebration of the Naval Victories of the Spanish-American War, Forbes Lithographers, 1898 (Folder OS FF 516)
      - The Harbor of the City of New York, after C. Graham, 1898 (Folder *OS FF 523)
        *Super oversize, fragile, requires special handling.
      - The New East River Bridge, Reinhardt, 1898 (Folder *OS FF 523)
      - New York and Williamsburg Bridge (Bridge No. 2), lithograph by Joseph Koehler, 1903 (Folder OS FF 518)
      - The New Singer Building in its Relation to the Sky-Line of New York, photogravure from photo by Irving Underhill, 1905 (Folder OS FF 518)
      - The College of the City of New York, photogravure by A.W. Elson & Co. after Richard Rummell, published by W.T. Littig, 1907 (Folder OS FF 518)
        City College, CUNY
      - Pennsylvania Station, New York City, printed by Ketterlinus after Hughson Hawley, 1910 (Folder *OS FF 523)
        *Super oversize.
        3 copies, 2 are fragile. Requires special handling.
      - Woolworth Building, New York, circa 1913 (Folder OS FF 518)
      - Hotel Marlborough, H.A. Thomas and Wiley Lithography Co. (Folder OS FF 519)
      - Joseph Hecht & Sons, Hides, Skins & Tallow [92-98 Cliff St.], J. Ottoman Lithographing Co. (Folder OS FF 519)
      - Home Office, Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., Madison Square, New York, American Lithographic Co. (Folder OS FF 519)
      - A South Prospect of Ye Flourishing City of New York in the Province of New York in America, 1717, engraving by John Harris after William Burgis (Folder OS FF 520)
        Five FACSIMILES
    - Manhattan - Oversize Photographs
      - Hester Street from Norfolk Street, photograph, circa 1890 (Folder OS FF 521)
      - Aerial view of East River and shoreline of Queens, photograph by Geo. R. Lawrence Co., Chicago, 1909 (Folder *OS FF 523)
        There are 3 mylar overlays taped to the image, with text and arrows highlighting various landmarks.
      - Aerial view of New York City from the tip of Manhattan, photograph by Skyviews Survey Inc., 1946 (Folder OS FF 521)
      - Aerial view of New York City from the tip of Manhattan, photograph by Skyviews Survey Inc., 1966 (Folder OS FF 521)
      - Aerial view of New York City from the tip of Manhattan, photograph by Skyviews Survey Inc., 1975 (Folder OS FF 521)
      - Aerial view of the East River showing shorelines of Manhattan and Queens, and the tip of Roosevelt Island, photograph by Skyview Surveys, Inc., 1979 (Folder OS FF 521)
      - Equitable Life Assurance Society building, photograph (Folder OS FF 521)
      - [Fifth Avenue] Holland House and Ardley Club Public Road Coach "Pioneer," 1904 (Folder OS FF 521)
      - St. John the Evangelist Church, West 11th Street, interior photograph (Folder OS FF 521)
      - Brooklyn Bridge, photograph (Folder *OS FF 523)
        printed from damaged negative
      - Brooklyn Bridge Looking North from the East River, panoramic photograph (Folder *OS FF 736)
        OS FF 736 is a custom container for 3 oversize panoramic photographs.
      - Brooklyn Bridge Tower, panoramic photograph by J.H. Beals (2 copies), 1876 (Folder *OS FF 736)
      - [Lower Manhattan from Brooklyn] (Folder OS FF, Item 2N / Unit 1A / top)
        Black & white; 1970s; 10 x 77.5 inches.
        [In enclosure with two other photographs.]
      - Manhattan Panorama: Hudson River from 14 th St & Houston St [1895-1900] (Folder OS FF, Item 2N / Unit 1A / top)
        Damaged, brittle,broken; 18 x 84 inches.
- Series II: New York City Views - the Bronx
  Series II New York City Views - the Bronx is arranged in an organizational structure by topic of the view. GENERAL views include aerial views (those taken from airplanes or from the top of a tall building) and birds-eye views (generally 19th-century prints).
  Harbor views are those which show the shore and skyline from the water, or from across some body of water. Some river and harbor views that show more than one borough are filed here. If the view is mainly of another borough, it will be filed therein.
  BUILDINGS are prints or photographs that spotlight a specific building. Churches and houses of worship are filed alphabetically by name
  NOTE: Churches and Synagogues may also include temples, other houses of worship, convents, retreat houses, and cemeteries. Government buildings include police and fire stations. Residences are filed alphabetically by the last name of the owner, or by their own name, if applicable. Cross-references have been provided in those cases. Named apartment complexes are filed in alphabetically with residences, and unnamed apartment buildings can be found at the end of the run.
  EVENTS include views of special events, such as parades, funeral processions, celebrations, and fairs. Material housed flat has been separated into two categories based on format: Prints and Photographs. Within each format, material has been arranged into the above categories. Each image filed under the Buildings categories is separately listed in the finding aid below. In other categories, attempts have been made to provide more specific information about images in each folder, to reduce browsing and encourage more specific use.
  - Subseries IIA: BRONX - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Bronx - Boxed Material - General Views
      - Aerial Views (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - General views (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Bronx River views (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Bridge views (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Leggett's Creek views (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Pelham Naval Station views (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Street Views
      - Streets A-B (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Bathgate Avenue (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Boston Road (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Streets C-E (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - East Chester Road (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Streets F-G (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Fenton Avenue (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Forest Avenue (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Franklin Avenue (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Grand Concourse (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Streets H-L (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Kingsbridge Road (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Streets M-O (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Melrose Avenue (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Mosholu Parkway (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Mott Avenue (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Streets P-S (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Pelham Parkway (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Pennyfield Avenue (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Prospect Avenue (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Sedgwick Avenue (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Streets T-W (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Tremont Avenue (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Waring Avenue (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Washington Avenue (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Webster Avenue (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Westchester Avenue (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - West Farms Road (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - White Plains Road (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Streets X - Z (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Numbered Avenues (includes third avenue) (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - 132nd - 149th street (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - 150th - 169th street (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - 170th - 179th street (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - 180th - 189th street (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - 190th - 210th street (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 211th - 249th street (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Unidentified street scenes (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Neighborhoods
      - City Island (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Spuyten Duyvil (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Throgs Neck (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Cemeteries
      - Cemeteries (A-Z) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Parks
      - Parks (A-Z) (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Bronx Park, including Botanical Gardens, Bronx Museums (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Bronx Zoological Park (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Crotona Park (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Drake Park (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Pelham Bay Park (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Van Cordlandt Park (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Buildings
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues (Box 4, Folder 12-22)
      - Buildings- Clubs and Organizations (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Government-General (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Government-Fire Houses (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Hotels A-Z (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
      - Buildings-Institutions- HospitalsA-Z (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Shelter for Delinquent Boys (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Manufacturing and Warehouses (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Monuments and Statuary (Box 5, Folder 11-13)
      - Buildings-Residences-A - C (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Residences-Bartow-Pell Mansion, Pelham Bay Park (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Residences-Bathgate, Charles Residence, West Farms (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Residences-D - F (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Residences-Ferris Houses (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Residences-Fox Estate (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Buildings-Residences-G - L (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Buildings-Residences-Hadley House (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Buildings-Residences-Hunt Mansion (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Buildings-Residences-Lorillard Mansions and Snuff Mill (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Buildings-Residences-M - N (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Residences-Morris, Gouverneur Mansion (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Residences-Morris, William H. Mansion and Estate (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Residences-O - S (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Residences-Poe, Edgar Allen, Cottage (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Residences-Poole, Townsend House (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Residences-T - V (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Residences-Van Cortlandt Mansion (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Residences-W - Z (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Residences-Zbrowski (Zabriskie) Mansion, Claremont Park (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Residences-Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Restaurants (A-Z) (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Taverns (A-Z) (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Schools-Primary and Secondary (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Colleges and Universities (including NYU and Manhattan College) (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
      - Buildings-Sports Stadia-Yankee Stadium (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Transportation Stations (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Buildings- Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Utilities
      - Utilities (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Transportation
      - Bus and Trolleys (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Railroads (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Third Avenue Elevated Railroad (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Events
      - Blizzard of Dec. 27, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Bronx Borough Day (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Parades (including firemen) (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
    - Bronx - Boxed Materials - Unidentified photos (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Subseries IIB: BRONX - FLAT MATERIAL
    - Bronx - Flat Material - Views
      - Aerial Views (Folder FF451)
        includes aerial views of Tremont, the West Bronx, and City Island.
      - General Views - Prints (Folder FF452)
        includes: 1891 auction map of lots for sale in 23rd Ward, near St. Mary's Park
        "A View of Phillip's Manor and the Rocks on the Hudson," from a drawing dated 1784
        "View of Melrose and Surroundings taken from the Ursuline Convent," 1868
        Mott Haven, showing Mott Iron Works
        1896 auction map of lots for sale at Underwood Terrace, Morris Heights, 24th ward
        "Historical Morrisania (Village)," 1861. Three versions, one with color
        "Plan of E.C. Cooper's Patent Inclined Plane Salt Works," City Island, East River, circa 1835
        "Fairmount Atheneum. Lewis Terrace, West Morrisania" undated
        "Car tracks, Cars, and Wagons on Third Avenue, Morrisania...and location of posts for proposed elevated railroad," 1881.
      - General Views - Photos (Folder FF453)
        West Farms Village
        Kingsbridge
        Spuyten Duyvil
        St. Ann's Avenue
        Washington Avenue
        Westchester Avenue
        Throgg's Neck Bridge approach
        unidentified open air theater, Mott Haven
        A. Hupfel's Sons Brewery, St. Ann's Avenue
      - Views - Grand Concourse, 1895-1897 (Folder FF453.5)
        Birds-eye views and street views (prints) produced by the Department of Street Improvements, showing the plans for the construction of the Grand Concourse.
      - Views - Parks and Gardens (Folder FF454)
        Bronx Park, photo by Elwin R. Sanborn, circa 1900
        Macomb's Dam Park, athletic field, circa 1910
        Old Snuff Mill in Bronx Park (now within Bronx Botanical Gardens)
        Van Cortland Mills in Van Cortland Park, photo by Edward Wenzel, 1893
        Van Cortland Mills in Van Cortland Park, unidentified photographer
        Van Cortland's Park, 1st-23rd- 71st Regiments [military encampment], 1917
    - Bronx - Flat Material - Buildings
      - Churches (Folder FF455)
        St. Ann's Protestant Episcopal Church, St. Ann's Avenue ca. 1873
        St. Edmund's Church, 176th Street
        St. Paul's Chapel, St. Ann's Parish, Morrisania
        St. Peter's Church, Westchester Avenue 1879-80
        Ursuline Convent, East Morrisania
        West Farms Reformed Church, Boston Road 1898
      - Clubs and Organizations (Folder FF456)
        Sibberns' Club House, Jerome Avenue
        Tremont YWCA
      - Government Buildings - Firehouses (Folder FF457)
        Independence Engine Co. #1, Williamsbridge
        Lady Washington Engine Co. #1, Fulton St.
      - Government Buildings - Municipal Building (Folder FF458)
        consists of photographs of the Bronx Municipal Building, later called Bronx Borough Hall. It was designed by George Post and completed in 1897. Demolished 1969.
      - Hotels (Folder FF459)
        photographs of Drovers Inn
        Nolans' Hotel
        Thwaite's Homestead Hotel
      - Residences - A-L (Folder FF460)
        Dr. Anderson House, Throgg's Neck, print
        Ashe-Leland-Van Scheck-Mitchell-Huntington House, photo by Nash, 1905
        Bailey, N.P. House, Fordham, two photolithographs
        Bartow House, Pelham Bridge Road, photo by Nash
        Berrian-Johnson House, Spuyten Duyvil Parkway, photo by Nash, 1906
        Bourne, D.B. House, photo by Nash, 1904
        Faile, E.G., "Locusts" House, photo by Nash, 1905
        Faile, E.G., "Woodside" House
        Ferris Houses, three photos by Nash, 1904-05
        Fox-Tiffany House, Westchester Avenue, photo circa 1895.
      - Residences - G-P (Folder FF461)
        Hadley House, Kingsbridge, photo by Nash, 1903
        Horton Farmhouse, City Island, photo by Nash, 1903
        Husted House, 221st Street, photo by Nash, 1903
        Hutchins, Waldo, Kingsbridge, photo by Nash, 1906
        Macomb, Robert House, Kingsbridge, photo by Nash, 1904
        Marshall House, City Island, photo by Nash, 1904
        Mathewson, Douglas House, 2024 Creston Avenue, drawing, circa 1911
        Miller House, Newton Ave, photo by Nash, 1906
        Montgomery Cottage, Fort Independence Avenue, photo by Nash, 1905
        Pell, Joshua House, Pelham, photo by Nash, 1904
        Poe, Edgar Allen, Cottage, photo by Edward Wenzel, 1893
        Poe, Edgar Allen, Cottage, 1902
        Poe, Edgar Allen, Cottage, circa 1910
        Powell Farmhouse, Washington Avenue, photo by Nash, 1904
      - Residences - Q-Z (Folder FF462)
        Randall House, 1323 Franklin Avenue
        Spy House, Morrisania, photo by Nash, 1905
        Stanton House, Washington Avenue, photo by Nash, 1904
        Tippett Mansion, Riverdale Avenue, photo by Nash
        Valentine-Cornell Homestead, photo by Nash, 1903
        Van Cortlandt Manor, 1905
        Varian, Isaac, Van Cortlandt Avenue, photo by Nash, 1901
        Wilkens, Walter House, Prospect Avenue, photo circa 1899
        Wilkins Farmhouse, Unionport, photo by Nash, 1904
        Williams, John House, 215th Street, photo by Nash, 1903
      - Residences - Ellis (Folder FF463)
        interior and exterior views of the home of John Stoneacre Ellis. includes photos of Ellis' collection of European arms and armor.
      - Residences - Morris (Folder FF464)
        various mansions and estates of the Morris family.
      - Residences - Vyse Manor (Folder FF465)
        Vyse family house on their estate called "Rocklands."
      - Residences - Other (Folder FF466)
        photos of houses taken by George W. Nash, 1903-1904.
      - Schools and Colleges (Folder FF467)
        Grammar School #5 (later #64), Webster Avenue 1890
        Fordham University
        Manhattan College (lithograph)
    - Bronx Flat - Material - Events
      - Borough Day Parade, 1915 (Folder FF468)
      - Breaking ground for subway construction, Westchester Avenue, 1916 (Folder FF468)
  - Subseries IIC: BRONX OVERSIZE MATERIAL
    - Birds Eye View of the Proposed Speedway Concourse in Wards 24 and 25 [Bronx], 1892 (Folder *OS FF 523)
      Grand Concourse.
- Series III: New York City Views - Brooklyn
  Series III New York City Views - Brooklyn is arranged in an organizational structure by topic of the view. GENERAL views include aerial views (those taken from airplanes or from the top of a tall building) and birds-eye views (generally 19th-century prints).
  - Subseries IIIA: BROOKLYN - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Brooklyn - Boxed Material - Aerial Views
      - Aerial & Bird's Eye Views (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn - Boxed Material - General Views
      - General views (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Waterfront views (piers) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Navy Yard (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Fort Hamilton (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Fort Lafayette (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn - Boxed Material - Street Views
      - Streets-A (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Atlantic Avenue (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Streets-B (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Bedford Avenue (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Blake Avenue (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Streets-C (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Clarkson Avenue (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Clinton Street (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Coney Island Avenue (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Court Street (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Streets-D (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Driggs Avenue (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Dumont Avenue (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Streets-E (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - East New York Avenue (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Streets-F (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Flatbush Avenue (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Fulton Street (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Streets-G (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Streets-H (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Humboldt Street (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Streets-I (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Streets-J (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Streets-K (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Kings Highway (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Kent Avenue (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Streets-L (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Streets-M (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Manhattan Avenue (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Metropolitan Avenue (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Montague Street (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Streets-N (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Neck Road (Gravesend Neck Road) (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - New Lots Road (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Nostrand Avenue (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Streets-O (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Ocean Avenue (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Streets- P-Q (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Paerdegat Street (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Pierrepont Street (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Pitkin Avenue (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Streets-R (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Ralph Avenue (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Rockaway Avenue (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Rogers Avenue (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Streets-S (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Snyder Avenue (Box 4, Folder 6)